dzyngiri.com 2013-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Dzyngiri

At dzyngiri.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by dzyngiri.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, dzyngiri.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information can be linked to information that is personally identifiable (i.e. when you comment or contact us via one of our forms).

### Dzyngiri respects your privacy.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Dzyngiri.

### Credit card details

Dzyngiri will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Dzyngiri.

### External Sites.

Dzyngiri is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

### Cookies ****

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Dzyngiri to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Dzyngiri does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

### Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Dzyngiri and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Dzyngiri have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.dzyngiri.com/?page_id=5).

This policy is valid from 07 December 2012
